Now that our butter and sugar have been fully mixed.
It is time to add the eggs; we are going to add two eggs but one at a time.
We are going to mix each one fully before we add the second.
Be careful when adding each egg; make sure you don't get any shell in there.
Start mixer off slowly before speeding it up a bit, the important thing when mixing it is that the egg yolk breaks before you speed it up this will help ensure you are not splattering the egg.
Let's speed it up.
And when we need to scrape down the side a bit before adding the next egg.
Right now there is lots of sugar in there compared to the amount of egg so it is not really changing the consistency very much but making it a bit wet.
Now we are going to add our second egg.
And then we are going to do what we did with the first one we are going to mix it in fully before going to the next step.